

Sergey Talabko

PROJECT MANAGER

Contacts

- 9 Levanevskogo St., Kiev, 03058
- sergey.talabko@gmail.com
- youtube.com/c/timteccomua
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/se rgey-talabko-48465a242/
- +38 096 500 50 49

Skills

Tech-savvy

Detail-attentive

Committed

Empathetic

About

Experienced in creating and setting up robotics and automation systems.

Possessing a strong technical and communication expertise that allows to analyze underlying processes at the client's side, plan corresponding solutions, articulate those to implementation teams and manage the development lifecycle.

Languages: EN(B2)/UA/RU

Education History

Mechanical engineer

Sep 2003- Jun 2007

National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

• Designing machines and mechanisms

Robotic programming

Nov 2016 -Dec 2016

FANUC Ukraine LLC

- · Basic programming course
- · Working with peripheral equipment course

Work Experience

TimTec Group

Jan 2014 - Feb 2022

CEO

- Driving the process of creation and starting up robotics welding systems
- Design, production, marketing, clients, finances, accounting

InnaLabs

Sep 2011 - Jun 2012

Head of balancing department

- Design of the wave gyroscope balancing system
- · Creating an automatic balancing algorithm

ROBUD GROUP

Apr 2010 - Sep 2011

Chief engineer-designer

 Design and commissioning of the ring formwork production line